Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Administrative Correspondence, 1927-1989, undated, Series 1:; (51 linear ft.)
  - General Correspondence, 1932-1983, undated, 1.1:
    - Art Journal, 1967-1978 (Reel 5327, Frame 885-910)
    - ART L...-ART NA (Reel 5327, Frame 911-922)
    - Art News, 1935-1978 (Reel 5327, Frame 923-1059)
    - ART NEWS A...-ART SH... (Reel 5327, Frame 1060-1087)
    - Art Sources, Inc., 1972-1976, undated (Reel 5327, Frame 1088-1139)
    - Art Students League, 1937-1977, undated (Reel 5327, Frame 1140-1215)
    - ART T...-ART W... (Reel 5327, Frame 1216-1237)
    - Artext Prints, Inc., 1947-1950 (Reel 5327, Frame 1238-1250)
    - ARTH-ARTIST (Reel 5327, Frame 1251-1255)
    - Artists Equity Association, 1947-1970 (Reel 5327, Frame 1256-1314)
    - Artists for Victory, 1942-1946, undated (Reel 5327, Frame 1315-1518)
    - ARTISTS G...-ARTISTS T... (Reel 5327, Frame 1519-1542)
    - Arts and Antiques Show, 1945 (Reel 5328, Frame 5-34)
    - ARTS AND C...-ARTS AND D... (Reel 5328, Frame 35-39)
    - Arts Club of Chicago, 1943 (Reel 5328, Frame 40-44)
    - Arts Club of Washington [D.C.], 1947-1948 (Reel 5328, Frame 45-67)
    - Arts Council [of Winston-Salem, N.C.], 1981 (Reel 5328, Frame 68-71)
    - Arts Digest, 1932-1955 (Reel 5328, Frame 72-137)
    - Arts, Education and America, 1976 (Reel 5328, Frame 138-139)
    - Arts Magazine, 1958-1975, undated (Reel 5328, Frame 140-184)
    - Arwin Galleries, 1962-1973 (Reel 5328, Frame 185-253)
    - Arzac, Daniel N., 1970-1971 (Reel 5328, Frame 254-259)
    - ASA-ASHA (Reel 5328, Frame 260-277)
    - Ashbrook, J. B., 1956-1976 (Reel 5328, Frame 278-298)
    - Asher, Leonard M., 1965-1977 (Reel 5328, Frame 290-303)
    - Asher, Leonard M., cont., 1965-1977 (Reel 5328, Frame 305-323)
    - Ashforth, Henry A., 1961-1979 (Reel 5328, Frame 304)
    - Ashforth, Henry A., cont., 1961-1979 (Reel 5328, Frame 324-374)
    - ASH-ASP (Reel 5328, Frame 375-389)
    - Associated American Artists, 1937-1953, 1974-1976, undated (Reel 5328, Frame 390-639)
    - Associated Councils of the Arts, 1973-1984 (Reel 5328, Frame 640-672)
    - Associated Dealers in American Art, 1947-1949, undated (Reel 5328, Frame 673-700)
    - ASSOCIATED H...-ASSOCIATED S... (Reel 5328, Frame 701-719)
    - Association for Advancing Contemporary Artists, 1932-1933 (Reel 5328, Frame 720-739)
    - ASSOCIATION FOR H...-ASSOCIATION OF... (Reel 5328, Frame 734-742)
    - AST-ATK (Reel 5328, Frame 743-753)
    - Atlanta Art Association (High Museum), 1933-1967 (Reel 5328, Frame 757-1072)
    - Atlanta University, 1957-1969 (Reel 5328, Frame 1073-1082)
    - Atlantic-Richfield, 1968-1982 (Reel 5328, Frame 1083-1113)
    - ATT-AUC (Reel 5328, Frame 1114-1130)
    - Audubon Artists, 1945-1978 (Reel 5328, Frame 1131-1273)
    - Augusta [Georgia] Art Club, 1939-1947 (Reel 5328, Frame 1274-1324)
    - AUGUSTE-AYER, E. (Reel 5328, Frame 1325-1421)
    - Ayer, N. W., 1940-1948 (Reel 5328, Frame 1422-1541)
    - Ayer, N.W., cont., 1948-1977 (Reel 5329, Frame 5-164)
    - AYR (Reel 5329, Frame 165-172)
    - BAB-BAL (Reel 5329, Frame 173-254)
    - Baldwin, 1945-1960 (Reel 5329, Frame 255-315)
    - Balis, Ann [Signora Emilio Orecchia], 1961-1963 (Reel 5329, Frame 316-328)
    - Balis, C. Wanton, 1960-1981 (Reel 5329, Frame 329-368)
    - BALL-BALLA (Reel 5329, Frame 369-392)
    - Ballard, Kay, 1961-1976, undated (Reel 5329, Frame 393-429)
    - BALLE-BALT (Reel 5329, Frame 430-449)
    - Baltimore Museum of Art, 1934-1962 (Reel 5329, Frame 450-602)
    - BANC -BANKS (Reel 5329, Frame 603-764)
    - BANN-BARB (Reel 5329, Frame 765-820)
    - Barclay McClelland (Art Products), 1932-1935 (Reel 5329, Frame 832-895)
    - Barclift (Reel 5329, Frame 821-831)
    - BARD-BARO (Reel 5329, Frame 896-1005)
    - BARR-BARTLE (Reel 5329, Frame 1006-1051)
    - BARTLETT-BARY (Reel 5329, Frame 1052-1080)
    - Basement Storage, 1948, undated (Reel 5329, Frame 1081-1169)
    - BASN-BAST (Reel 5329, Frame 1170-1207)
    - BAT (Reel 5329, Frame 1208-1288)
    - BAU-BEA (Reel 5329, Frame 1289-1378)
    - Bechtel, Stephen D., 1957-1982 (Reel 5329, Frame 1379-1413)
    - BECK-BECKL (Reel 5329, Frame 1414-1472)
    - BE-BELL (Reel 5329, Frame 1473-1544)
    - BELL, cont. (Reel 5330, Frame 6-11)
    - Beloit College, 1943-1957 (Reel 5330, Frame 12-49)
    - Bemis, Francis, 1937-1973, undated (Reel 5330, Frame 50-111)
    - BENE-BENTL (Reel 5330, Frame 112-160)
    - Benton & Bowles, 1940-1955 (Reel 5330, Frame 161-205)
    - Benton, William (Encyclopedia Britannica) (see also: Encyclopedia Britannica), 1961-1973 (Reel 5330, Frame 206-256)
    - BENZ-BERE (Reel 5330, Frame 257-268)
    - Berg, Bert, 1939-1962 (Reel 5330, Frame 269-320)
    - BERGD-BERGER, N. (Reel 5330, Frame 321-331)
    - Berger, Sidney, 1954-1976 (Reel 5330, Frame 332-360)
    - BERGER, W.-BERGT (Reel 5330, Frame 361-395)
    - BERKE-BERKOWITZ, H. (Reel 5330, Frame 396-422)
    - Berkowitz, Rosalie (Art Consultant), 1959-1975 (Reel 5330, Frame 423-444)
    - BERKOWITZ, S.-BERL (Reel 5330, Frame 445-503)
    - BERM-BERN (Reel 5330, Frame 504-550)
    - BERR-BERT (Reel 5330, Frame 551-583)
    - BES (Reel 5330, Frame 584-601)
    - Beth El Temple [West Hartford, Conn.], 1972-1982 (Reel 5330, Frame 602-650)
    - BETHERS (Reel 5330, Frame 651-652)
    - Bethesda Art Gallery, 1975-1980 (Reel 5330, Frame 653-673)
    - BERTHL-BID (Reel 5330, Frame 674-691)
    - Biel, Erwin, 1959-1965 (Reel 5330, Frame 692-748)
    - BIEN-BIN (Reel 5330, Frame 749-794)
    - Biographies of Artists (A-Z), undated (Reel 5330, Frame 795-821)
    - Birmingham Museum of Art (Birmingham Art Association), 1947-1981 (Reel 5330, Frame 822-1069)
    - BIRMINGHAM P...-BLA (Reel 5330, Frame 1070-1169)
    - BLE-BLOCK, H. (Reel 5330, Frame 1170-1200)
    - Block, Leonard, 1962-1977 (Reel 5330, Frame 1201-1234)
    - BLOCK, M.-BLOOMINGDALE, A. (Reel 5330, Frame 1235-1249)
    - Bloomingdale's, 1946-1957, undated (Reel 5330, Frame 1250-1315)
    - Bloomington [Ill.] Art Association, 1941-1955 (Reel 5330, Frame 1316-1407)
    - BLOOMS-BLUM, M. (Reel 5330, Frame 1408-1463)
    - Blum, Mr. and Mrs. Robert, 1961-1980 (Reel 5330, Frame 1464-1509)
    - BLUM'S-BOARD OF EDUCATION, FREEPORT, N.Y. (Reel 5330, Frame 1510-1552)
    - Board of Education of New York City (see also: New York City, Board of Education), 1948-1971 (Reel 5331, Frame 5-69)
    - BOB-BOH (Reel 5331, Frame 70-92)
    - Boise Art Association, 1949-1965 (Reel 5331, Frame 93-158)
    - BOL-BOO (Reel 5331, Frame 159-242)
    - BOR-BOSS (Reel 5331, Frame 243-282)
    - Boston Arts Festival, 1956-1959, undated (Reel 5331, Frame 283-328)
    - BOSTON AT...-BOV (Reel 5331, Frame 329-427)
    - Boston, Museum of Fine Arts (see: Museum of Fine Arts, Boston) (Reel 5331)
    - BOWD-BOWLE (Reel 5331, Frame 428-482)
    - Bowling Green State University-Art Dept., 1951-1973 (Reel 5331, Frame 483-507)
    - BOWM-BRAI (Reel 5331, Frame 508-608)
    - BRAM-BRAR (Reel 5331, Frame 609-689)
    - BRAS-BRECH (Reel 5331, Frame 690-745)
    - Breckenridge, Robert, 1968-1975 (Reel 5331, Frame 746-784)
    - BRECKER-BRESLA (Reel 5331, Frame 785-819)
    - F. H. Bresler, Co., 1947, 1962 (Reel 5331, Frame 820-858)
    - BRESN-BREY (Reel 5331, Frame 859-877)
    - BRIC-BRIO (Reel 5331, Frame 878-932)
    - Brisacher, 1940-1943, undated (Reel 5331, Frame 933-952)
    - BRISK-BRIT (Reel 5331, Frame 953-997)
    - BROA-BROG (Reel 5331, Frame 998-1036)
    - BRON-BROOKLI (Reel 5331, Frame 1037-1071)
    - Brooklyn Museum, 1933-1976, undated (Reel 5331, Frame 1072-1356)
    - Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, 1933-1979 (Reel 5331, Frame 1357-1557)
    - Brooks Memorial Art Gallery, cont., 1933-1979 (Reel 5332, Frame 5-47)
    - BROOKS-BROU (Reel 5332, Frame 48-70)
    - BROWN, A.-BROWN, L. (Reel 5332, Frame 71-155)
    - BROWN, A.-BROWN, L., cont. (Reel 5332, Frame 256-257)
    - Brown, Margaret (Gallery), 1949-1954 (Reel 5332, Frame 156-186)
    - BROWN, R.-BROWN, W. (Reel 5332, Frame 187-198)
    - Brown & Bigelow, 1941-1957 (Reel 5332, Frame 199-215)
    - BROWNE-BROWNING, E. (Reel 5332, Frame 216-223)
    - Browning, Louise, 1964-1977 (Reel 5332, Frame 224-253)
    - BRU-BUCHANAN, G. (Reel 5332, Frame 259-308)
    - Buchanan, Dr. and Mrs. J. Robert, 1966-1961 (Reel 5332, Frame 309-337)
    - BUCHS (Reel 5332, Frame 338-341)
    - Buck Hill Art Association, 1944-1962 (Reel 5332, Frame 342-415)
    - BUCKL-BUCKN (Reel 5332, Frame 416-439)
    - Budworth & Son, 1932-1961, undated (Reel 5332, Frame 440-506)
    - BUF-BUI (Reel 5332, Frame 507-523)
    - Builders, 1950-1958 (Reel 5332, Frame 524-811)
    - BUIM-BUN (Reel 5332, Frame 812-826)
    - BURA-BURR (Reel 5332, Frame 890-986)
    - Burrelle's Press Clipping Service, 1939-1953 (Reel 5332, Frame 827-889)
    - BURRO-BUS (Reel 5332, Frame 987-1049)
    - BUTLER, A. (Reel 5332, Frame 1474)
    - Butler Art Institute, 1939-1981, undated (Reel 5332, Frame 1050-1472)
    - BUTLER, P.-BYRNES (Reel 5332, Frame 1475-1527)
    - CA-CAI (Reel 5332, Frame 1528-1559)
    - CAJ-CALIFORNIA M... (Reel 5333, Frame 5-28)
    - California Palace of the Legion of Honor, 1943-1965 (Reel 5333, Frame 29-112)
    - CALIFORNIA PO...-CALV (Reel 5333, Frame 113-140)
    - CAM (Reel 5333, Frame 141-211)
    - CANAD (Reel 5333, Frame 212-220)
    - Canajoharie Public Library, 1964-1978 (Reel 5333, Frame 221-249)
    - CANAL-CANP (Reel 5333, Frame 250-262)
    - Canton Art Institute, 1944-1960 (Reel 5333, Frame 268-317)
    - CAP-CARLEN (Reel 5333, Frame 263-267)
    - CAP-CARLEN, cont. (Reel 5333, Frame 318-386)
    - Carleton College, 1943-1960 (Reel 5333, Frame 387-427)
    - CARLS-CARNEGIE H... (Reel 5333, Frame 428-449)
    - Carnegie Institute, 1933-1983 (Reel 5333, Frame 450-1219)
    - Carnegie Study of the Arts of the United States (Reel 5333, Frame 1220-1243)
    - CARNEY-CARR (Reel 5333, Frame 1244-1294)
    - Carreau, Cyrille, Real Estate (re: 605 Madison Ave.) (see also: Midtown Galleries (605 Madison Ave.), 1935-1947 (Reel 5333, Frame 1295-1421)
    - CARREL-CARRI (Reel 5333, Frame 1422-1426)
    - Carroll-Knight Gallery, 1947 (Reel 5333, Frame 1427-1446)
    - CARROLL R...-CARY (Reel 5333, Frame 1447-1491)
    - CAS-CAT (Reel 5333, Frame 1492-1566)
    - CAV-CEDAR C... (Reel 5334, Frame 5-58)
    - Cedar Rapids Art Association, 1940-1980 (Reel 5334, Frame 59-196)
    - CEDARH-CENTN (Reel 5334, Frame 197-262)
    - CENTR-CENTU (Reel 5334, Frame 263-357)
    - CHAF-CHAM (Reel 5334, Frame 358-411)
    - CHAN-CHAPPELL (Reel 5334, Frame 412-495)
    - Chappellier Gallery, 1952-1978, undated (Reel 5334, Frame 496-579)
    - CHAR-CHASE, I. (Reel 5334, Frame 580-655)
    - Chase National Bank (Chase Manhattan Bank), 1944-1982 (Reel 5334, Frame 656-790)
    - CHASE, R.-CHASES (Reel 5334, Frame 791-795)
    - Chattanooga Art Association, 1934-1968, undated (Reel 5334, Frame 796-848)
    - CHATH-CHERO (Reel 5334, Frame 849-874)
    - Cherry, James, 1935-1979 (Reel 5334, Frame 875-975)
    - CHES (Reel 5334, Frame 976-977)
    - Chicago Art Club, 1954 (Reel 5334, Frame 978-979)
    - Chicago, Art Institute of (see also: Art Institute of Chicago), 1942-1975 (Reel 5334, Frame 980-1220)
    - Chicago, Art Institute of, cont. (see also: Art Institute of Chicago), 1942-1975 (Reel 5334, Frame 1495-1572)
    - CHICAGO T...-CHRIST (Reel 5334, Frame 1221-1298)
    - CHRISTI-CHRYSLER CO. (Reel 5334, Frame 1299-1342)
    - Chrysler Museum, 1958-1963 (Reel 5334, Frame 1343-1385)
    - CHRYSLER, W.-CINA (Reel 5334, Frame 1386-1413)
    - Cincinnati Art Museum, 1934-1979 (Reel 5335, Frame 5-197)
    - CINCINNATI, U...-CITT (Reel 5334, Frame 1414-1449)
    - City Art Museum of St. Louis (see also: St. Louis, City Art Museum of), 1957-1966 (Reel 5334, Frame 1450-1475)
    - CITY C...-CIV (Reel 5334, Frame 1476-1494)
    - CLAI-CLARK (Reel 5335, Frame 198-248)
    - Clary, Robert, 1955-1981, undated (Reel 5335, Frame 249-327)
    - CLAU-CLAY (Reel 5335, Frame 328-343)
    - Clearwater Art Museum, 1943-1950 (Reel 5335, Frame 344-381)
    - CLEM-CLEVE (Reel 5335, Frame 382-405)
    - Cleveland Health Museum, 1946-1947 (Reel 5335, Frame 406-445)
    - Cleveland Institute of Art, 1956-1974 (Reel 5335, Frame 446-499)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, 1935-1981 (Reel 5335, Frame 500-557)
    - CLEVER-CLIF (Reel 5335, Frame 558-561)
    - Climenko, Jesse, 1933-1983 (Reel 5335, Frame 562-581)
    - Clinical Communications, Inc., 1968-1969 (Reel 5335, Frame 582-607)
    - CLO-CLY (Reel 5335, Frame 608-618)
    - COA-COG (Reel 5335, Frame 619-650)
    - COH (Reel 5335, Frame 651-751)
    - Coker College, 1959-1960 (Reel 5335, Frame 752-767)
    - COLB (Reel 5335, Frame 768-792)
    - Colby College, 1947-1976 (Reel 5335, Frame 793-897)
    - COLE (Reel 5335, Frame 898-938)
    - COLEM-COLLAB (Reel 5335, Frame 939-981)
    - Collar, Donald R., 1972-1975 (Reel 5335, Frame 982-988)
    - Collections, 1942-1951, undated (Reel 5335, Frame 989-1032)
    - COLLECTOR-COLLECTORS R... (Reel 5335, Frame 1033-1050)
    - College Art Association of America, 1933-1952 (Reel 5335, Frame 1051-1187)
    - COLLEGE OF...-COLLIE (Reel 5335, Frame 1088-1197)
    - COLLIN-COLOR (Reel 5335, Frame 1198-1216)
    - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, 1939-1946 (Reel 5335, Frame 1217-1322)
    - Colorado Springs Fine Arts Center, cont., 1946-1970, undated (Reel 5336, Frame 5-121)
    - Colorado, University of, 1948-1975 (Reel 5336, Frame 122-196)
    - COLT-COLUMBIA G... (Reel 5336, Frame 197-203)
    - Columbia [S.C.] Art Association (Columbia Museum of Art), 1934-1981, undated (Reel 5336, Frame 204-334)
    - Columbia Pictures (re: Barrabas) (Reel 5336, Frame 335-437)
    - Columbia University, 1936-1972 (Reel 5336, Frame 438-455)
    - Columbus [Georgia] Art Association (Columbus Museum of Arts and Crafts, Inc.), 1944-1975 (Reel 5336, Frame 456-543)
    - Columbus [Georgia] Art Association (Columbus Museum of Arts and Crafts, Inc.), cont., 1944-1975 (Reel 5336, Frame 546-551; 555)
    - COLUMBUS D... (Reel 5336, Frame 556-558)
    - Columbus [Ohio] Gallery of Fine Arts (Columbus Museum of Art), 1941-1983 (Reel 5336, Frame 544-545)
    - Columbus [Ohio] Gallery of Fine Arts (Columbus Museum of Art), cont., 1941-1983 (Reel 5336, Frame 552-554)
    - Columbus [Ohio] Gallery of Fine Arts (Columbus Museum of Art), cont., 1941-1983 (Reel 5336, Frame 559-903)
    - Columbus, Ohio State Fair, 1976-1977 (Reel 5336, Frame 904-1014)
    - COM-CONA (Reel 5336, Frame 1015-1054)
    - Conboy, B. J., 1955-1982 (Reel 5336, Frame 1055-1078)
    - CONC-CONL (Reel 5336, Frame 1079-1109)
    - CONN (Reel 5336, Frame 1110-1154)
    - CONO-CONS (Reel 5336, Frame 1155-1167)
    - CONT (Reel 5336, Frame 1168-1210)
    - CONV-CONW (Reel 5336, Frame 1211-1222)
    - COO-CORB (Reel 5336, Frame 1223-1288)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1934-1962 (Reel 5336, Frame 1289-1571)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art, cont., 1962-1972 (Reel 5337, Frame 1-149)
    - CORCORAN, J.-CORNELL G... (Reel 5337, Frame 150-163)
    - Cornell University, 1940-1983 (Reel 5337, Frame 164-225)
    - Corning Museum of Glass, 1956-1957 (Reel 5337, Frame 226-250)
    - Cornish, Marcella G., 1973-1975 (Reel 5337, Frame 251-269)
    - CORO-COSMOPOLITAN C... (Reel 5337, Frame 270-297)
    - Cosmopolitan, 1948-1973 (Reel 5337, Frame 298-313)
    - Costigan, Mrs. Richard J., 1957-1981 (Reel 5337, Frame 314-342)
    - COT-COURT (Reel 5337, Frame 343-387)
    - Courvoissier Galleries, 1937-1941 (Reel 5337, Frame 388-432)
    - COUS-COWE (Reel 5337, Frame 433-472)
    - Cowie Galleries, 1946-1952 (Reel 5337, Frame 473-517)
    - COWL-COY (Reel 5337, Frame 518-535)
    - CRAF-CRAM (Reel 5337, Frame 536-546)
    - Cranbrook Academy of Art, 1940-1974 (Reel 5337, Frame 547-730)
    - CRANE-CRAW (Reel 5337, Frame 731-759)
    - Creative Art, 1932-1942, undated (Reel 5337, Frame 760-785)
    - CREATIVE ARTI...-CRIS (Reel 5337, Frame 786-809)
    - Critics, Art, 1933-1942, undated (Reel 5337, Frame 810-907)
    - Crocker Art Gallery, 1941-1949 (Reel 5337, Frame 908-959)
    - CROCKER, H.-CRY (Reel 5337, Frame 960-1008)
    - CUE-CULB (Reel 5337, Frame 1009-1034)
    - Cullen, William, 1959-1980 (Reel 5337, Frame 1035-1093)
    - CULP (Reel 5337, Frame 1094-1095)
    - Cummer Gallery of Art, 1962-1971 (Reel 5337, Frame 1096-1163)
    - CUMMI-CUN (Reel 5337, Frame 1164-1200)
    - CURI-CURL (Reel 5337, Frame 1201-1205)
    - Curran, Cathie, 1973-1982 (Reel 5337, Frame 1206-1243)
    - CURRI-CURRIER, A. (Reel 5337, Frame 1244-1248)
    - Currier Gallery of Art, 1937-1972 (Reel 5337, Frame 1249-1396)
    - CURT-CUSHI (Reel 5337, Frame 1397-1425)
    - Cushman Gallery, Inc., 1956-1958 (Reel 5337, Frame 1426-1448)
    - CUSHMAN, P.-CUT (Reel 5337, Frame 1449-1462)
    - CZ-DALLAS F... (Reel 5337, Frame 1436-1522)
    - Dallas Health Museum, 1947-1948 (Reel 5337, Frame 1523-1541)
    - Dallas Museum for Contemporary Arts, 1958 (Reel 5337, Frame 1542-1544)
    - Dallas Museum of Fine Arts, 1935-1970, undated (Reel 5338, Frame 5-276)
    - DALLAS N...-DANA (Reel 5338, Frame 277-331)
    - Dana Museum and Park (see: De Cordova Museum) (Reel 5338)
    - DANCE I...-DANCE P... (Reel 5338, Frame 332-361)
    - DANI-DARTE (Reel 5338, Frame 362-447)
    - Dartmouth College, 1943-1952 (Reel 5338, Frame 448-500)
    - DAS-DAVENPORT, L. (Reel 5338, Frame 501-512)
    - Davenport Municipal Art Gallery, 1939-1970, undated (Reel 5338, Frame 513-744)
    - DAVENPORT S...-DAVID, A. (Reel 5338, Frame 745-750)
    - David Strawn Art Gallery (Jacksonville [Fla.] Art Association; see also: Strawn, David, Art Gallery), 1940-1947 (Reel 5338, Frame 751-784)
    - David, W., 1963 (Reel 5338, Frame 785-786)
    - Davidner, Mark, 1982 (Reel 5338, Frame 787-788)
    - Davidson College, 1973-1975 (Reel 5338, Frame 789-817)
    - DAVIDSON, H.-DAVIES (Reel 5338, Frame 818-858)
    - DAVIS-DAY (Reel 5338, Frame 859-941)
    - Dayton Art Institute, 1934-1974 (Reel 5338, Reel 942-1178)
    - DEA-DEB (Reel 5338, Frame 1179-1209)
    - Decatur [Ill.] Art Center, 1944-1963 (Reel 5338, Frame 1210-1244)
    - DECH-DECORA (Reel 5338, Frame 1245-1393)
    - Decoration, Interior and Window Display (see also: Decorators; Window Displays), 1934-1942 (Reel 5339, Frame 5-26)
    - Decorators (see also: Decoration, Interior and Window Display; Window Displays), 1941-1956, undated (Reel 5339, Frame 27-98)
    - De Cordova Museum (and Dana Museum and Park), 1962-1977 (Reel 5339, Frame 99-153)
    - DEE-DELAR (Reel 5339, Frame 154-188)
    - Delaware Art Museum, 1971-1975 (Reel 5339, Frame 189-205)
    - DELAWARE B...-DELAWARE D... (Reel 5339, Frame 206-209)
    - Delaware, University of, 1962-1980 (Reel 5339, Frame 210-241)
    - Delgado Museum of Art (see: Isaac Delgado Museum of Art) (Reel 5339)
    - DELG-DENT (Reel 5339, Frame 242-291)
    - Denver Art Museum, 1934-1967 (Reel 5339, Frame 292-442)
    - DEP-DESIGN C... (Reel 5339, Frame 443-481)
    - Design, 1948-1964 (Reel 5339, Frame 482-493)
    - DESIL-DESK (Reel 5339, Frame 494-502)
    - Des Moines Art Center (Edmundson Art Foundation), 1933-1971 (Reel 5339, Frame 503-843)
    - DES MOINES AS...-DETRI (Reel 5339, Frame 844-853)
    - Detroit Institute of Arts, 1937-1969 (Reel 5339, Frame 854-983)
    - DEU-DE YOUNG, J. (Reel 5339, Frame 984-1017)
    - De Young Memorial Museum, 1938-1953, undated (Reel 5339, Frame 1018-1200)
    - DIA-DIAMOND (Reel 5339, Frame 1201-1212)
    - Diamondstein Book Co., 1962-1973 (Reel 5339, Frame 1265-1346)
    - DIC-DIL (Reel 5339, Frame 1213-1264)
    - DIN-DL (Reel 5339, Frame 1347-1375)
    - DOA-DOO (Reel 5339, Frame 1376-1427)
    - DOR-DOT (Reel 5339, Frame 1428-1579)
    - Doubleday, Inc., 1941-1981 (Reel 5340, Frame 5-237)
    - DOUG-DOWNS (Reel 5340, Frame 238-309)
    - Downtown Gallery, 1932-1953 (Reel 5340, Frame 310-335)
    - DOY (Reel 5340, Frame 336-339)
    - DRAC-DRAWING M... (Reel 5340, Frame 340-366)
    - Drawing Society, 1961-1975, undated (Reel 5340, Frame 367-409)
    - DRE (Reel 5340, Frame 410-420)
    - Dreyfus, M. (Reel 5340, Frame 463-477)
    - Dreyfuss, Henry, 1947-1962, undated (Reel 5340, Frame 421-462)
    - DRI-DUBR (Reel 5340, Frame 478-501)
    - Dubuque Art Association, 1938-1954 (Reel 5340, Frame 502-547)
    - DUC-DUF (Reel 5340, Frame 548-580)
    - Duke University, 1964-1976 (Reel 5340, Frame 581-609)
    - DUKS-DUN (Reel 5340, Frame 610-627)
    - Dunbar Corporation, 1952-1977 (Reel 5340, Frame 628-694)
    - DUNC-DUNN (Reel 5340, Frame 695-773)
    - DUP-DUX (Reel 5340, Frame 774-819)
    - DW-DY (Reel 5340, Frame 820-828)
    - EA (Reel 5340, Frame 830-967)
    - Edmundson Art Foundation (see: Des Moines Art Center) (Reel 5340)
    - EB-EI (Reel 5340, Frame 968-1050)
    - EL (Reel 5340, Frame 1051-1109)
    - EMA-EMPLE (Reel 5340, Frame 1110-1170)
    - Employees [Midtown], 1937-1973, undated (Reel 5340, Frame 1172-1372)
    - EMPO (Reel 5340, Frame 1373-1374)
    - Encyclopedia Britannica (see also: Benton, William), 1945-1957 (Reel 5340, Frame 1375-1517)
    - ENE-ESK (Reel 5340, Frame 1518-1578)
    - Esquire, 1936-1966, undated (Reel 5341, Frame 5-69)
    - ESSEN (Reel 5341, Frame 80-81)
    - Essex [Conn.] Art Association, 1947-1949 (Reel 5341, Frame 82-93)
    - Essex Co. [N.J.] Section, National Council of Jewish Women (see also: National Council of Jewish Women, Essex Co. [N.J.] Section), 1968-1977 (Reel 5341, Frame 94-120)
    - EST-EVANG (Reel 5341, Frame 121-187)
    - Evansville Public Museum, 1946-1968 (Reel 5341, Frame 188-252)
    - EVEN-EVERG (Reel 5341, Frame 253-262)
    - Everhardt Museum of Natural History, Science, and Art, 1955-1960 (Reel 5341, Frame 263-324)
    - Everson Museum of Art, 1956-1968 (Reel 5341, Frame 325-349)
    - EW-EY (Reel 5341, Frame 350-392)
    - FAB-FAI (Reel 5341, Frame 393-435)
    - FAL-FAN (Reel 5341, Frame 436-473)
    - FAR-FARK (Reel 5341, Frame 474-521)
    - Farleigh Dickinson University, 1945-1979 (Reel 5341, Frame 522-544)
    - FARLEY (Reel 5341, Frame 545-549)
    - Farnsworth Art Museum, 1947-1981 (Reel 5341, Frame 550-635)
    - FARRA-FARRE (Reel 5341, Frame 636-658)
    - Farrow, Richard S., 1964-1982 (Reel 5341, Frame 659-700)
    - Fashion Fair, 1947-1948 (Reel 5341, Frame 701-730)
    - FAST-FAY (Reel 5341, Frame 731-750)
    - Faulkner Memorial Art Gallery (see: Santa Barbara Free Public Library) (Reel 5341)
    - FEA-FEDERATED (Reel 5341, Frame 751-775)
    - Federation of Modern Painters and Sculptors, Inc., 1942-1970 (Reel 5341, Frame 776-812)
    - FEI-FELDE (Reel 5341, Frame 813-850)
    - Feldman, Charles, 1938-1953 (Reel 5341, Frame 851-913)
    - FELDMAN, J.-FEN (Reel 5341, Frame 914-947)
    - FER-FET (Reel 5341, Frame 948-1011)
    - FIA-FIG (Reel 5341, Frame 1012-1041)
    - Fillin, Walter, 1931, 1960-1981 (Reel 5341, Frame 1042-1112)
    - FILM-FIN (Reel 5341, Frame 1113-1185)
    - First National B.. (Reel 5341, Frame 1186-1257)
    - First National City Bank, 1954-1974 (Reel 5341, Frame 1258-1316)
    - FIRST P...-FIT (Reel 5341, Frame 1317-1359)
    - FLA-FLEISCH (Reel 5341, Frame 1360-1373)
    - Fleischman, Lawrence A., 1954-1967 (Reel 5341, Frame 1374-1417)
    - FLEISH-FLINT, G. (Reel 5341, Frame 1418-1445)
    - Flint Institute of Arts, 1952-1975 (Reel 5341, Frame 1446-1521)
    - FLOC-FLORIDA A... (Reel 5341, Frame 1522-1529)
    - Florida Gulf Coast Art Center, 1949-1951 (Reel 5341, Frame 1530-1560)
    - Florida Gulf Coast Art Center, cont., 1951-1956, undated (Reel 5342, Frame 5-56)
    - FLORIDA I...-FLY (Reel 5342, Frame 57-108)
    - Fogg Art Museum, 1933-1979 (Reel 5342, Frame 109-207)
    - FOL-FON (Reel 5342, Frame 208-250)
    - Foote, Cone and Belding, 1946-1956, undated (Reel 5342, Frame 251-278)
    - Foothills Art Center, Inc., 1976-1980 (Reel 5342, Frame 279-331)
    - Forbes, 1968-1972 (Reel 5342, Frame 332-398)
    - FORBES, M.-FORD AND... (Reel 5342, Frame 399-428)
    - Ford Foundation, 1958-1962 (Reel 5342, Frame 429-490)
    - FORE (Reel 5342, Frame 491-497)